In time, losing consciousness, organs, fins, and eyes,
Male and female merge into a single life form.
A torn goldfish scooping net,
The lantern’s dim light rolls, peeking through as it bleeds
My soaked hair drips
I wanted the festival music in the air to be far away
Go far away, toward where no one is
In this sea, humans become coral,
swallowed by the void and infinite darkness
Paradise lies deep below
Don't let go, hold me and sink
To the depths where even the moon can’t be scooped
Just like a deep-sea anglerfish
I wish I could light a love in the pitch-black abyss
Let's drift together
In the future we won't be alone
We'll become "us," melting together as we live on
You will join with me
And I will eventually transform into "us"
As if flowing, our two lives sink into one body
Until we reach the field of graves
With no destination, and not knowing how to return
A one-way ticket, guided by a lantern called hope
Time moves on, the journey continues
Let's dive deeper, let's go on without fearing the darkness
Even if we never find what we’re looking for
Just like a deep-sea anglerfish
I hope I'm buried beneath corpses falling headfirst into the future
If you wish for it, look. An encore
This corpse can be revived at any time
Even if it's ugly, it melts and lives on
The moon is just like...
A lantern hung by the Earth, isn't it?
Ah, I see
We were already one
Floating, sinking, even if we're clumsy
I just want to live
Just like a deep-sea anglerfish
I wish I could light a love in the pitch-black abyss
I hope I’m buried beneath corpses falling headfirst into the future
Just like a deep-sea anglerfish
We’re moving forward, relying on hope
It's okay if we can't return
Just like a deep-sea anglerfish, where to?
Let's go as far as we can
Remaining as "us"
Just living on