dammit
Woah, my heart's beating. Do you like me, like me?
Ah... my heart's throbbing. Die, die, die, die!
I want that blue ribbon,
I don't wanna come in second place.
Everybody's parting ways with me cause I'm so annoying.
Being a handful is unpopular. Why? Why? Why?
I'm lost. I'm at a loss and I'm feeling lost.
The girl who never gets chosen... I'm gonna die!
Psycho? The psycho is... which, which one?
The only thing I can believe in... is your face!
Yeah, I'm not doing that. I can't deal with that.
Lonely for life, thanks for your good vibes.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE! taka-ta-tat-ta!
ok for real,
That good love feeling, you like it? You like it?
That good in-love feeling, you like it? You like it?
The Do Re Mi's are scary... Cherry-cherry
That "I don't think so" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?
That "I don't care" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?'
Your thorns are scary... Baby-baby
That good love feeling, you like it? You like it?
That good in-love feeling, you like it? You like it?
How convenient! Cherry-cherry.
That "I don't think so" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?
That "I don't care" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?'
Let's come back to this later, Baby-baby.
No, like... really
Woah, my heart's beating. Do you like me, like me?
Ah... my heart's throbbing. Die, die, die, die!
Yay, heart is beatin’, d’you love me, love me?
I want that blue ribbon,
I don't wanna come in second place.
Hey teacher, what's it mean to like someone?
Give me words that aren't in any dictionary.
I hold back my anger and apologize - "I'm sorry."
Your "liking" isn't "liking," I'm gonna throw up!
You hopeless idiot, go away.
I'm waiting for my Prince Charming
Yeah, I'm not doing that. I can't deal with that.
Make sure to disinfect! Salute to pureness
Didn’t do it, can’t keep doin’ it
Lonely for life, thanks for your good vibes.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
Ok for real,
sigh…
taka-ta-tat-ta!
...Ok for real,
That good love feeling, you like it? You like it?
That good in-love feeling, you like it? You like it?
The Do Re Mi's are scary... Cherry-cherry.
That "I don't think so" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?
That "I don't care" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?'
Your thorns are scary... Baby-baby.
That good love feeling, you like it? You like it?
That good in-love feeling, you like it? You like it?
How convenient! Cherry-cherry.
That "I don't think so" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?
That "I don't care" feeling, is that a 'no way, no way?'
Let's come back to this later, Baby-baby.
'Kay, it's break-time!
Woah, my heart's beating. Do you like me, like me?
Ah... my heart's throbbing. Die, die, die, die!
Ready, go!!
Translation by Tamanegi-P
Amendments by ilovesteak32