Please use PC/Mobile Browser!
Come on, gimme gimme more
:-b ;-b boy, :-b ;-b boy, duh
Bleh!
Check me out, study and don me,
don don don
Mleh, Bleh!
Ugh! Your face’s subtitles say, “You so dumb”, dumb dumb
So let’s
Double-doubt dance,
like boogie-woogie
Lost and lonely,
devil devil
Serve up your heart on a platter,
raise it high high
Sad trombone
Eggshellin’ dance,
like boogie-woogie
Gotchu all figured,
yeah gimme gimme
And your answer is?
Hi hi
“It was just casual”, b**ch,
say what?
Gonna STOP you right there. No chemistry? You messin’
Been so stoked for puberty, bring it!
Say “I wanchu”, can’t hear that scream!
Let’s make contractual love go viral, matchings
Green-lighting this heart, let me rehearse it
Amateur at playing live, gosh darn it!
Sigh, “A Hopeless Romantic Has A Dream!”
Surprise! An anime version! Lookin’ forward to it
Unhappy endings are such letdowns
“feat. YOU”, come on, gimme gimme more
:-b ;-b boy, :-b ;-b boy, duh
Come on
I know you know,
but you ghost me,
that’s what I’m sayin’
Come on
I hate you,
can’t get there,
I’m not strong
enough
So let’s
Freak out and talk, on edge on edge
Hard fought chance, like devil devil
Your manuscript’s due, yes hi hi
So let’s
Bluff and talk, on edge on edge
Bet on money love, I’ve got debit debit
Please give me a clean sweep, yes hi hi
Waaaaaat the f**k??
Gonna STOP you right there. Bet against the odds? You messin’
Going in for the win and missing, every time!! Sick of it
That “I wanchu”, can’t nobody hear it
Packed full of telepathy, zapping
Delusional till the end, gotta get my revenge
Love shall avenge the Emperor!
Sigh, “I Got Reincarnated as Me”
“Then go say three words to a wall.” Yup! That’s my jam!
Unhappy endings are such letdowns
“feat. YOU”, come on, gimme gimme more
:-Duh yeah, :-D ;-Duh yeah
Say “I wanchu”, can’t hear that scream!
Unhappy endings are such letdowns
“feat. YOU”, come on, gimme gimme more
This program is brought to you
by the following sponsors: